realityoffers.com 2018-08-30

# Adult Internet Deals Reality Offers™

This Privacy Policy, as may be amended from time to time, governs your use of RealityOffers.com (collectively, the "Site", "we" or "us"). As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it

_Adults Only Service_

**THIS IS AN ADULTS _ONLY_ SERVICE**. We will suspend or terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Site; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person. 

_California Residents_

If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name and email address, the URL for the website you visited, and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Please mail your request to postmaster@secureprovide.com. 

_Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety_

All information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to assist or comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system whether in connection with an open investigation or in connection with reporting a suspected crime. 

_Information That May Be Collected From You_

During sign up we require that you provide certain information which may include Account Data (e.g., username, email address, gender, profile preferences, and password) and "Demographic Information" (e.g., IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history). 

_How Is This Information Used by the Site?_

Registration Data  
We use your Account Data to establish and maintain your account with the Site as well as to send you alerts regarding available deals which may be of interest to you. We may use "cookies" and Demographic Information to improve your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Site according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Account and Demographic Information. Demographic Information concerning our users may be shared with or sold to third parties who may offer products or services which may be of interest to you. We may also share aggregate, non-individual Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving the Site. 

_You Are Responsible For Information You Provide to Third Parties_

Financial Data  
We will never collect any payment information from you. Any purchase you make in response to an email advertisement or an advertisement posted on the Site will require you to submit your payment information directly to the third party from whom you are making your purchase or such third party's payment processor, as applicable. Any information you provide to such third party(ies) will not be governed by this Privacy Policy. Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party's terms and conditions and privacy policy. 

_Emails From Us and Use of Your Email Address_

Your email address will be used to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. As set forth above, we may share or sell your email address to third parties. Information from us may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information relating to your use of the Site. Third parties with whom we share or to whom we sell your email address may email you from time to time regarding various offers or services which are unrelated to us. We and these third parties may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to the Site until such time as you advise the appropriate sender of such emails, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive emails. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us and do not wish for your email address to be shared with any additional third parties please notify us by using this link: <http://clk.secureprovide.com/unsubscribe/> or send us an email to abuse@secureprovide.com If your account is active and you elect to opt out of emailings, your account with the Site may be terminated. We fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all emails from us will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receiving further email correspondence. Please note we will never send you an email directly or indirectly without your consent. **Please immediately report to us any email you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purports to promote the Site or relates to the Site in any other way. To make a report, please forward a copy of the email to: abuse@secureprovide.com.**

_Advertisements_

We may utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or to place, host and/or server ads on the Site for services or goods offered by third parties. Either we or the advertising agencies may use cookies and/or "action tags" to measure advertising effectiveness on an anonymous basis and to ensure rotation of advertisements. Some emails from us may contain advertisements from businesses unrelated to the Site. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertiser's website. Also, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies of any business with advertisements appearing anywhere on the Site or brought to your attention through the Site or any email from the Site or those who receive your email address from the Site, regardless of whether or not there may be any mention of, or references to, the Site on such business's website. 

_Changes to the Privacy Policy_

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of any such change. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the Privacy Policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless such change to the Privacy Policy has clear language indicating otherwise. 

_Changes in Ownership of the Site_

The Site is a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including, but not limited to, in connection with a merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate, facilitate and/or complete any such transaction(s).
